Kellar, J. Sergeant First Class,
serial number 7178412.
Iran, Guatemala, Colombia, Croatia.
Very impressive.
I know what you're trying to do, sir.
It ain't going to work.
No, Sergeant Kellar. You don't know
what I'm trying to do.
I'm here to clean up this mess.
If you cooperate.
If...
I walk out that door,
everything you did will be declassified.
You will be convicted.
You will be discharged.
You will spend the rest of your life in prison.
Very well, Sergeant.
Have it your way.
Wait.
What do you want me to do?
Tell me everything you know about Seventh Wave.
Weapons dealers, heavy hitters,
dealing mostly in high-spec former
Eastern Bloc hardware.
Clients began to include terrorist cells.
Seventh Wave was escalated to priority status
after they took out nine agency spooks.
Coordinated executions.
Division 1 and Seventh Wave taken out
with extreme prejudice.
Intel zeroed out on three possible targets.
Valencia was the boss; Ruben and Yev Dejanka
were the muscle.
Three teams were tasked with overwatch
until it was time to take them out.
I had one of those teams.
Intel suspected the Brits, Chinese and Israelis
had teams in the area.
Everyone was after these guys.
Who was the fourth man?
Gunfire.
Didn't think much of them at the time.
What went wrong?
We got made.